[TRAIN RATTLES IN DISTANCE]
[♪♪♪]
♪ I found a love ♪
♪ For me ♪
♪ Darling, just dive right in ♪
♪ And follow my lead ♪
♪ Well, I found a girl ♪
♪ Beautiful and sweet ♪
♪ Oh, I never knew you were
that someone waiting for me ♪
♪ Cos we were just kids
when we fell in love ♪
♪ Not knowing what it was ♪
♪ I will not give you up
this time ♪
♪ Darling, just kiss me slow ♪
♪ Your heart is all I own ♪
♪ And in your eyes,
you're holding mine ♪
♪ Baby, I'm... ♪
♪ Dancing in the dark ♪
♪ With you between my arms ♪
♪ Barefoot on the grass ♪
♪ Listening to
our favourite song ♪
♪ When you said
you looked a mess ♪
♪ I whispered
underneath my breath ♪
♪ But you heard it ♪
♪ Darling,
you look perfect tonight ♪
♪ Well, I found a woman ♪
♪ Stronger than anyone I know ♪
♪ She shares my dreams ♪
♪ I hope that someday
I'll share her home, oh ♪
♪ I found a lover ♪
♪ To carry more
than just my secrets ♪
♪ To carry love,
to carry children of our own ♪
♪ We are still kids,
but we're so in love ♪
♪ Fighting against all odds ♪
♪ I know we'll be alright
this time ♪
♪ Darling, just hold my hand ♪
♪ Be my girl, I'll be your man ♪
♪ I see my future in your eyes ♪
♪ Baby, I'm... ♪
♪ Dancing in the dark ♪
♪ With you between my arms ♪
♪ Barefoot on the grass ♪
♪ Listening to
our favourite song ♪
♪ When I saw you in that dress,
looking so beautiful ♪
♪ I don't deserve this ♪
♪ Darling,
you look perfect tonight ♪
♪ (Darling, oh) ♪
♪ Baby, I'm... ♪
♪ Dancing in the dark ♪
♪ With you between my arms ♪
♪ Barefoot on the grass ♪
♪ Listening to
our favourite song ♪
♪ I have faith in what I see ♪
♪ Now I know I have met
an angel in person ♪
♪ And she looks perfect ♪
♪ I don't deserve this ♪
♪ You look perfect tonight ♪
[♪♪♪]