(birds chirping)
(church bells ringing)
(engine revving)
- It's December 6, 2014.
We're gonna drive LA and hit
every wedding we possibly can.
It's gonna be awesome and we're late.
(engine revving)
(tyres squealing)
Let me get your door for you.
- Thanks, man.
(engine revving)
- Woohoo!
- Let's do it!
(upbeat music)
(people indistinctly talking)
♪ I'm hurting, baby ♪
♪ I'm broken down ♪
♪ I need your loving, loving ♪
♪ I need it now ♪
♪ When I'm without you ♪
♪ I'm something weak ♪
♪ You got me begging, begging ♪
♪ I'm on my knees ♪
♪ I don't wanna be needing your love ♪
♪ I just wanna be deep in your love ♪
♪ And it's killing me when
you're away, ooh, baby ♪
♪ 'Cause I really don't
care where you are ♪
♪ I just wanna be there where you are ♪
♪ And I gotta get one little taste ♪
♪ Your sugar ♪
♪ Yes, please ♪
♪ Won't you come and put it down on me ♪
♪ I'm right here 'cause I need ♪
♪ Little love, a little sympathy ♪
♪ Yeah, you show me good loving ♪
♪ Make it alright ♪
♪ Need a little sweetness in my life ♪
♪ Your sugar ♪
♪ Yes, please ♪
♪ Won't you come and put it down on me ♪
♪ My broken pieces ♪
♪ You pick them up ♪
♪ Don't leave me hanging, hanging ♪
♪ Come give me some ♪
♪ When I'm without ya ♪
♪ I'm so insecure ♪
♪ You are the one thing, one thing ♪
♪ I'm living for ♪
♪ I don't wanna be needing your love ♪
♪ I just wanna be deep in your love ♪
♪ And it's killing me when
you're away, ooh, baby ♪
♪ 'Cause I really don't
care where you are ♪
♪ I just wanna be there where you are ♪
♪ And I gotta get one little taste ♪
♪ Your sugar ♪
♪ Yes, please ♪
♪ Won't you come and put it down on me ♪
♪ I'm right here ♪
♪ 'Cause I need ♪
♪ Little love, a little sympathy ♪
♪ Yeah, you show me good loving ♪
♪ Make it alright ♪
♪ Need a little sweetness in my life ♪
♪ Your sugar ♪
♪ Sugar ♪
♪ Yes, please ♪
♪ Won't you come and put
it down on me, yeah ♪
♪ I want that red velvet ♪
♪ I want that sugar sweet ♪
♪ Don't let nobody touch it
unless that somebody's me ♪
♪ I gotta be your man ♪
♪ There ain't no other way ♪
♪ 'Cause girl you're hotter
than a southern California day ♪
♪ I don't wanna play no games ♪
♪ You don't gotta be afraid ♪
♪ Don't give me all that shy shit ♪
♪ No make-up on ♪
♪ That's my sugar ♪
♪ Yes, please ♪
♪ Won't you come and put it down on me ♪
♪ I'm right here, right here ♪
♪ 'Cause I need, 'cause I need ♪
♪ Little love, a little sympathy ♪
♪ So, baby, yeah you show me good loving ♪
♪ Make it alright ♪
♪ Need a little sweetness in my life ♪
♪ Your sugar ♪
♪ Sugar ♪
♪ Yes, please ♪
♪ Won't you come and put it down on me ♪
♪ Down on me ♪
♪ Sugar ♪
♪ Yes, please ♪
♪ Won't you come and put it down on me ♪
♪ Down on me ♪
♪ I'm right here 'cause I need ♪
♪ Little love, a little sympathy ♪
♪ Yeah, you show me good loving ♪
♪ Make it alright ♪
♪ Need a little sweetness in my life ♪
♪ Your sugar ♪
♪ Sugar ♪
♪ Yes, please ♪
♪ Won't you come and put it down on me ♪
♪ Down on me, down on me ♪
♪ Woo ♪
(upbeat music)
(people cheering)
- Good night, guys, thank you so much.
This was the coolest thing
ever, ever, ever, ever.
(people cheering)