♪♪♪
♪ SPENT 24 HOURS, I NEED
MORE HOURS WITH YOU ♪
♪ YOU SPENT THE WEEKEND
GETTING EVEN, OOH ♪
♪ WE SPENT THE LATE NIGHTS
MAKING THINGS RIGHT BETWEEN US ♪
♪ BUT NOW IT'S
ALL GOOD, BABE ♪
♪ ROLL THAT BACK WOOD, BABE ♪
♪ AND PLAY ME CLOSE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE GIRLS LIKE YOU RUN
'ROUND WITH GUYS LIKE ME ♪
♪ 'TIL SUN DOWN WHEN
I COME THROUGH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE
YOU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ GIRLS LIKE YOU LOVE FUN,
AND YEAH, ME TOO ♪
♪ WHAT I WANT WHEN
I COME THROUGH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE
YOU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH YEAH YEAH,
YEAH YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE
YOU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH YEAH YEAH,
YEAH YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE YOU ♪
♪ I SPENT LAST NIGHT ON
THE LAST FLIGHT TO YOU ♪
♪ TOOK A WHOLE DAY UP
TRYNA GET WAY UP, OOH ♪
♪ WE SPENT THE DAYLIGHT TRYNA
MAKE THINGS RIGHT BETWEEN US ♪
♪ BUT NOW IT'S
ALL GOOD, BABE ♪
♪ ROLL THAT BACK WOOD, BABE ♪
♪ AND PLAY ME CLOSE ♪
♪ 'CAUSE GIRLS LIKE YOU RUN
'ROUND WITH GUYS LIKE ME ♪
♪ 'TIL SUN DOWN WHEN
I COME THROUGH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE
YOU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ GIRLS LIKE YOU LOVE
FUN, AND YEAH, ME TOO ♪
♪ WHAT I WANT WHEN
I COME THROUGH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE
YOU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH YEAH YEAH,
YEAH YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE
YOU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH YEAH YEAH,
YEAH YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE
YOU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE YOU,
YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE YOU ♪
♪ MAYBE IT'S 6:45 ♪
♪ MAYBE I'M BARELY ALIVE ♪
♪ MAYBE YOU'VE TAKEN MY SHIT
FOR THE LAST TIME, YEAH ♪
♪ MAYBE I KNOW
THAT I'M DRUNK ♪
YOU'RE THE ONE ♪
♪ MAYBE YOU'RE THINKING
IT'S BETTER IF YOU DRIVE ♪
♪ OH 'CAUSE GIRLS LIKE YOU
RUN 'ROUND WITH GUYS LIKE ME ♪
♪ 'TIL SUN DOWN WHEN
I COME THROUGH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL
LIKE YOU, YEAH ♪
♪ NOT TOO LONG AGO I WAS
DANCIN' FOR DOLLARS ♪
♪ KNEW IT WAS REALLY REAL
IF I LET YOU MET MY MOMMA ♪
♪ YOU DON'T WANT A GIRL
LIKE ME I'M TOO CRAZY ♪
♪ BUT EVERY OTHER GIRL YOU
MEET IS FUGAZY (OOOKKURRT) ♪
♪ I'M SURE THEM OTHER
GIRLS WERE NICE ENOUGH ♪
♪ BUT YOU NEED
SOMEONE TO SPICE IT UP ♪
♪ SO WHO YOU GONNA
CALL CARDI CARDI ♪
♪ TO COME AND REV IT
UP LIKE A HARLEY HARLEY ♪
♪ WHY IS THE BEST FRUIT
ALWAYS FORBIDDEN ♪
♪ I'M COMING TO YOU NOW
DOIN' 20 OVER THE LIMIT ♪
♪ THE RED LIGHT
RED LIGHT STOP (STOP) ♪
♪ I DON'T PLAY WHEN IT COMES TO
MY HEART, LETS GET IT THOUGH ♪
♪ I DON'T REALLY WANT A
WHITE HORSE AND A CARRIAGE ♪
♪ I'M THINKING MORE WHITE
PORSCHES AND KARATS ♪
♪ I NEED YOU RIGHT HERE
CAUSE EVERY TIME YOU FALL ♪
♪ I PLAY WITH THIS KITTY LIKE
YOU PLAY WIT YOUR GUITAR ♪
♪ 'CAUSE GIRLS LIKE YOU RUN
'ROUND WITH GUYS LIKE ME ♪
♪ 'TIL SUN DOWN WHEN
I COME THROUGH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE
YOU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ GIRLS LIKE YOU LOVE
FUN, AND YEAH, ME TOO ♪
♪ WHAT I WANT WHEN
I COME THROUGH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE
YOU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH YEAH YEAH,
YEAH YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE
YOU, YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ YEAH YEAH YEAH,
YEAH YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE YOU ♪
♪ YEAH YEAH YEAH,
YEAH YEAH YEAH ♪
♪ I NEED A GIRL LIKE YOU ♪
♪♪♪