Just few years ago,
when i started to grow up
Met you in that afternoon, feeling amazed then turned speechless
You were pure and innocent, those sparkle eyes looks like never fall in love
Cause hesitate to speak out
so this love still lonely
You never know,
I'm always here
Seeing you far away
Times passing by
If that day i confessed my love to you
Would you trust me and take my hand
Together, we can go through all hard winter
If that day i were the one that you want
Whether it sunshine or raining
Now i had a beautiful story
Just few years ago, when i was growing
Met you in that afternoon, i went speechless
You were pure and innocent, those sparkle eyes looked like never fall in love
Cause scared to speak out, our love became lonely
You never know
I'm always here
Looking at your shadow are being faded
Time passing by...oh uh wahhh
If that day i confessed my love to you
Would you trust me and take my hand
We can go through all the pain
If that day i were the one that you want
Whether it's raining or sunshine
Now I had a beautiful story
Behind the smile for you, i walk away
Behind my laughing eyes, there's nothing but regret
Wind are blowing leaves this afternoon
Our love story put back in my dream
The sweet dream i gave you
If that day i confessed my love to you
Would you trust me and take my hand
Together go throught the winter
If that day i were the one that you always dreaming
Whether raining or sunshine
Now I had a beautiful story
Now i had...
Beautiful Story.